好，她们有水，柳橙汁…
All right,they got water,orange juice...
这个看起来像苹果汁
...and what looks like cider.
喝喝看吧
Taste it.
对，这是一杯油
Yeah,it's fat.
我喝了油！
I drank fat!
我知道，两分钟前我才喝过的
I know,I did that two minutes ago.
晚礼服先生
Hey,Mr. Tux.
你们怎么还没换衣服？ 还有半小时
-Why aren't you dressed? -We have a half-hour.
那是四分钟前的事 我们必须在七点四十出门
That was four minutes ago. We have to be out the door at 7:40.
放心，我们会准备好的 我们只要两分钟就着装完毕
Relax,we'll be ready. It takes us two minutes to get dressed.
若你现在就换好，我会高兴点
I'd feel better if you got dressed now.
好 好
-Okay. -Okay.
看看你，多性感啊
Oh,look at you. All sexy.
真的吗？
Really?
你怎么不早点过来？ 因为我真是笨得要命
-How come you didn't come over earlier? -Because I'm a stupid,stupid man.
罗斯，要不要来点苹果汁？
Hey,Ross,want some cider?
不要
No.
你快准备好了吧
So you're pretty close,huh?
妆化好了，头发梳好了
Makeup's on. Hair's done.
我只要换衣服就好了
I just have to get dressed.
大概只要6或7分钟吧
And that takes,what? Just 6 or 7 minutes?
是啊，只要我决定好要穿什么
Yeah. Once I figure out what I'm wearing.
要不要喝点油？
Glass of fat?
本集播出：“没有人准备好”
The One Where No One's Ready
怎么了？你是不是 因为要演讲而紧张？
What's the matter? You nervous about your speech?
不是
Nope.
你要不要听听看？ 里面有提到我吗？
-You wanna hear it? -Am I in it?
等我感谢完 所有捐钱给博物馆的人
After I thank everyone for donating to the museum...
我就唱一首歌 歌颂乔伊的伟大
... I sing a song about the wonder that is Joey.
嗨，你看起来真棒
Hello! You look great!
谢谢你 虽然我已经知道了
Thank you. I know,though.
看到没？ 这个人准备好，可以出发了
You see this? This is a person who is ready to go.
菲比，你…
Phoebe,you....
你真是我的偶像啊
You are my star.
那你就是我的幸运铜板
Well,you're my lucky penny.
好，我做了测验 结果是我把事业放在比男人重要的位置了
All right,I took the quiz. And it turns out I do put career before men.
起来
Get up.
什么？
What?
你坐在我的位子上 为何这是你的位子？
-You're in my seat. -How is this your seat?
因为我刚才坐在这里
I was sitting there.
但是你离开了
But then you left.
拜托，我又不是去西班牙
Well,it's not like I went to Spain.
我是去厕所 你明知道我会回来的
I went to the bathroom. You knew I'd be back.
那有什么大不了的 去坐别的地方嘛
What's the big deal? Sit somewhere else!
真正大不了的就是 我是最后坐在这里的人
The "big deal" is I was sitting there last! So...
所以这是我的位子
...it's my seat.
事实上，你最后坐的地方是那里，所以…
Well,actually,the last place you were sitting was in there,so....
各位，你们知道嘛？ 那个一点都不重要
You guys,you know what? It doesn't matter.
你们俩都必须 在我脑血管爆掉前换好衣服
You both have to go get dressed before the big vein in my head pops.
我只要再做一件事 这真的没什么大不了
I just have to do one thing. It's not a big deal.
起来！
Get up!
菲比，你看起来好美
Phoebe,you look great!
好啦，早知道了
All right already.
你要变魔术吗？
Are you gonna do magic?
真好笑，给我换衣服去
That's funny. Change.
慢点，我才刚进门 我才不管
-Hang on,I just got in. -I don't care.
晚会八点开始，我们不能迟到
It starts at 8. We can't be late.
他不能、不会、也不愿等
"He could not,would not,want to wait."
我们的桌子在前方 我老板也会在那儿
Our table is down in front. My boss will be there.
若晚会开始后我们才进场 大家都看得到
Everyone will see if we arrive after it starts.
有人喝过我这一杯油吗？
Has somebody been drinking my fat?
这像是古生物学家的女友 会穿的衣服吗？
Does this look like something a paleontologist's girlfriend would wear?
我不知道 你大概是首开先例吧
I don't know. You might be the first one.
瑞秋，你听答录机留言了吗？ 没有
-Rach,did you check the machine? -No.
等等，这件衣服 会显得我小腿很粗，算了
Wait. This is the outfit that makes my calves look fat. Never mind.
乔伊，我今天写了一首歌
Well,Joey,I wrote a little song today.
歌名叫做“起来”
It's called,"Get up!"
我希望我可以帮到你什么
l wish there was something l could do to help you.
起来……
Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up.
好啦，椅子给你啦
All right. You can have the chair.
真的？ 天啊，你看看这个（表示“不是真心的”）
-Really? -Oh,my. Would you look at that?
是我，我正要过去
It's me,I'm coming over.
若你播放这则留言时 我已经到了呢？
What if I'm already there when you play this message?
是不是很诡异？
Is that too spooky?
瑞秋，你在不在？ 是我，快接起来
Hi,Rach,are you there? It's me. Pick up.
瑞秋…？
Rachel? Rach?
干嘛？
What?
没事
Never mind.
嗨 瑞秋 我是你妹妹
Hi, Rach, it's your sister.
你有没有跟丹尼马志奥上过床？昨晚他叫个不停
Did you ever sleep with Donnie Mazzio because last night he kept shouting:
两个对两个
''Two for two. ''
你是想让我去穿衣服还是听一个关于夜间坐马车出游的长故事？
Do you want me to get dressed or hear a long story about a hayride?
你只问他吗？因为我们也…
Are you only asking him because....
莫妮卡，我是理查 打电话给我
Monica,it's Richard. Call me.
这则留言是新的还是旧的？
Is that message old or new?
新的还是旧的…？
Old or new? Old or new?
绝对是旧的 你没听到两声哔吗？
It's definitely old. Didn't you hear the double beep?
若是新的怎么办？ 我们说好不联络的
What if it's new? We agreed not to talk.
可能有重要的事 我该不该回电话？
It could be important. Shouldn't I call him back?
甜心，你已经打过了 这是旧的留言
Honey,you did call him back. It's old.
是啊，莫妮卡，你听着…
Yeah,see,Mon,listen. Listen.
当卡萝与我分手时
When Carol and I broke up...
我也经历一样的事 你知道我怎么做吗？
... I went through the same thing. You know what I did?
我去换好衣服
I got dressed.
真的要快一点，真的 好…
Really,really quickly,okay? Okay?
这就对了…
There we go. There we go.
你知道吗？别起来了 就坐在那里吧
You know what? Don't get up. Just sit there.
只希望你别介意我的手 放在这里
I just hope you don't mind my hand right here.
没碰到，不能生气 没碰到，不能生气
Not touching. Can't get mad! Not touching. Can't get mad!
没碰到，不能生气
Not touching. Can't get mad!
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
你们这些坏孩子！
You rotten boys!
抱歉，菲比 我该怎么办？
-Sorry,Phoebe. -What am I gonna do?
别乱抹 有什么可以去除豆泥？
Don't rub it! What gets out hummus?
有什么可以去除豆泥？
What gets out hummus?
莫妮卡！ 有什么可以去除豆泥？
Monica! What gets out hummus?
如果那个留言是新的 他到底打来说什么？
If it is a new message,what is he calling to say?
好，谢谢，我会试试看的
Okay,thanks. Yeah,I'll try that.
说不定他打来说 你执迷不悟而且太疯狂
Maybe he called to say you're obsessive and crazy?
我该不该回电话给他？ 不！
-So should I call him back? -No!
不！
No!
这些搭配吗
Okay, do these match?
-是的，很搭配 -不搭配
-Yes, they definitely match.-They don't match.
干嘛？ 他们不搭配
What? They didn't match.
很好，我们一起坐在椅子上 随便啊
-Fine,we'll both sit in the chair. -Fine with me.
我好舒服啊
I am so comfortable.
我也是
Me too.
事实上，我可能有点太舒服了
In fact,I think I might be a little too comfortable.
好，我们有19分钟 钱德，我要你去换衣服
Okay,we have 19 minutes. I want you to go and change.
等你回来后，乔伊去换衣服 他就会把椅子空出来
When you come back,Joey will go change and he'll have vacated the chair.
好 好的
-Okay. -All right.
好，我要走了
Fine. I'm going.
等我回来后这里就是 椅子城市，而我是…
When I get back,it's Chair City. And I'm the guy...
坐在椅子上的那个人！
...who's sitting in a chair!
这是不是有点太…
Is this a little too
菲比，怎么回事？
Pheebs? What happened?
我沾到豆泥了
I got the hummus.
甜心，我们会找出衣服给你 你要不要穿我的黑外套？
Oh,honey,we'll find you something. You wanna wear my black jacket?
这样跟裙子就不能搭配了 没错
-lt won't go with this dress. -You're right.
来吧我们把衣服换掉 不…可别换掉
-Well,let's just get you out of that. -No,no,no. Not "out of that."
千万别把衣服脱掉 莫妮卡 菲比可以借你的绿裙子穿吗？
-Not "out" of clothes. -Can Phoebe borrow your green dress?
我打给他了
I called him.
对，我进入他的答录机 然后我留言了
Yes. I got his machine and I left a message.
不过没关系…
But it's okay. It's okay...
因为那是个随兴，轻松的留言
... because it was,like,a casual,breezy message.
很轻松
It was breezy.
天啊，若听起来并不轻松 该怎么办？
Oh,God,what if it wasn't breezy?
怎么可能不轻松？ 不会，这里是个轻松的地方
How could it not be breezy? No. Because you're in such a breezy place.
我知道了，我播放我的留言 你们再告诉我是否轻松
I got it. I'll play my message and you guys tell me if it's breezy enough.
你怎么可能那样做？
But how you gonna do that?
我知道他答录机的密码
I know the code to his answering machine.
好，莫妮卡 我不认为现在应该…
Okay,Mon,I really don't think this is the
好，你在拨号了…
Okay,you're dialing. You are dialing.
-在干什么？ -莫妮卡正在进入理查的答录机
-What's going on?-Monica's beeping into Richard's machine.
她疯了吗
ls she crazy?
就像稻草
Like a straw.
记得吗？疯狂的稻草
Remember? Crazy straws?
我是理查 请在哔声后留言
Hi,this is Richard. Please leave a message at the tone.
你有两个新讯息
You have two new messages.
真是个好工作
What a cool job.
“你有两个新讯息”
"You have two new messages."
“请把馅饼递给我”
Please pass the pie.
我是莫妮卡 我只是想确定一下
Hi,it's Monica. I'm just checking in.
我有一通留言 不知道是新的还是旧的
I got a message and didn't know if it was old or new.
所以，我只是问问看
So I'm just checking.
告诉我吧
So let me know.
或者不告诉我，都可以
Or don't. Whatever.
我很轻松
I'm breezy!
你不能说“我很轻松” 这样就不轻松了
You can't say you're "breezy." That negates the "breezy."
你好啊，是我 昨天真是愉快
Hola. It's me. Yesterday was really fun.
打电话给我 谈谈周末的计划，好吗？
Call me about this weekend,okay?
看，她听起来就很轻松
Now,she sounded breezy.
他开始约会了 我真不敢相信他开始约会
He's seeing someone. I can't believe he's seeing someone.
你又不知道那个是谁 那么那是谁的声音？
-You don't know that. -Well,whose voice was that?
说不定是他妹妹的 说不定是他女儿的
Maybe it was his sister's. Maybe it was his daughter's.
蜜雪儿，一定是了！ 听起来像蜜雪儿吗？
Michelle. Of course! Did it sound like Michelle?
我记不清了
l cannot remember her.
太好了，开始下雨了 这样计程车又更难叫了
Oh,great. It's starting to rain. That'll make it easier to get a cab.
是蜜雪儿
It was Michelle.
绝对是蜜雪儿
It was definitely Michelle.
去试穿莫妮卡的绿裙子 不适合就穿我的灰色丝质的
Try Monica's green dress. If it doesn't fit,wear my gray silk one.
我要穿那件的 你还不知道自己要穿什么？
-Unless I wear it. -You don't know what you're wearing?
今晚是你的大日子 我只是希望自己好看一点
I'm just trying to look nice for your big night.
是啊，而我们在12分钟内 必须出门
Yeah,which we have to leave for in 12 minutes.
来吧，我帮你选衣服
Come on,I'll just pick something out for you.
-那件 那件，看起来很好 -罗斯，那是毛巾
-There! There! That looks good.-Ross, that's a towel!
你看到了，我全换好了
You'll notice that I'm fully dressed.
而我呢，也发现你 什么都还没换
I,in turn,have noticed that you are not.
所以用米尔恩（小熊维尼作者）的话说“离开我的椅子，驴蛋！”
So in the words of A.A. Milne,"Get out of my chair,dill-hole."
好
Okay.
你在干什么？ 你叫我离开椅子啊
-What are you doing? -You said to give you the chair.
你又没说不能带走椅垫
You didn't say anything about cushions.
但椅垫是椅子的精华所在
They're the essence of the chair!
没错，我要带走精华
That's right! I'm taking the essence.
他会回来的
Oh,he'll be back.
这里什么人也没有
Oh,there's nobody in the room.
对不起，我觉得这样很美 这是万圣节服装
-I'm sorry,I thought it looked pretty. -That was a Halloween costume.
除非你要我穿的像 小牧羊女一样？
Unless you would like me to go as Little Bo Peep.
若没有那只可充气的羊 我不会认出来
I didn't recognize it without that inflatable sheep.
是啊，对了，钱德 我最近想要一只回来
Yeah,which,by the way,Chandler,I would like back one of these days.
瑞秋，很好啊 这件是不是很适合我？
Rach,good! Listen,isn't this perfect for me?
太棒了！ 但是不适合今晚
Oh,it's perfect! But not for tonight.
当然不适合今晚 我要参加慈善晚会呢
Of course,not for tonight. Hi. I'm going to a benefit.
不适合今晚？ 那你在干嘛？
Not for tonight? What are you doing?
对不起，不是故意的 我爱你…深呼吸
No,I'm sorry. We didn't mean it. I love you. Breathe.
我们去露营时 把它们当枕头
We used them as pillows when we went camping.
什么？
What?
那些羊啊
The sheep.
你的闲暇时间在干嘛…
Hey,what you do on your own time....
我的内裤呢？
Where's my underwear?
拜托，你拿了他的内裤？ 他拿走我的精华啊
-Come on,you took his underwear? -He took my essence!
好，等等，你干嘛不穿 你现在身上的内裤？
Okay,hold on. Why can't you just wear the underwear you're wearing now?
因为我现在根本没有穿内裤
Because I'm not wearing any underwear now.
那你今晚为何要穿内裤？
Then why do you have to wear underwear tonight?
因为晚礼服是租的
It's a rented tux,okay?
我不想没穿内裤 就穿别人的衣服
I'm not gonna go commando in another man's fatigues.
那有人就得把椅垫还给别人
Then somebody's gonna have to give somebody back his cushions.
好，你把我衣服藏起来 我要做一件完全相反的事
Okay. You hide my clothes,I'm gonna do the exact opposite to you.
什么？难道你要 给我看我的衣服吗？
What,are you gonna show me my clothes?
相反的事…
Hey,opposite...
就是相反的事
...is opposite.
他什么都没有！
He's got nothing!
好，我准备好了
Okay,I'm ready.
瑞秋那儿没有我喜欢的 除了这个圣诞彩带
Rachel didn't have anything I liked but this ribbon.
我想，好吧 那我就政治化一点
I thought,all right,I'll be political.
那你在支持什么？ 当然是圣诞节
-What are you supporting? -Christmas.
我无所谓，已经搞定两个了 我还有整整12分钟
Hey,that's okay with me. Two down,and I have exactly 12 minutes
什么？
What?
我的表停了 我的表，好，你看…
My watch stopped. My watch. Okay,see...
这个恐龙指针的尾巴不动了
...the dinosaur tail isn't going around anymore.
现在几点？已经7点33分 我还有7分钟
What time is it? It's 7:33. I have 7 minutes.
我还有7分钟！
I have seven minutes!
我该穿哪一双鞋？ 黑色的还是紫色的？
Which shoes should I wear? The black or the purple?
随便挑一双，好吗？ 好啦，黑色的
-Just pick one,okay? -Oh,okay,okay. The black.
你有没有黑色的 然后有细带子的？
Do you have black with little strappies?
有，不过那种适合配裤子 或者我该穿裤子
Yeah. But those go better with pants. Maybe I should wear pants.
对了，穿裤子是好主意 或者不要穿裤子更好
Yeah,pants! What an idea! Or better yet,go without pants.
我不知道你在做什么 但是你快进去…
I don't know what you're doing,but just get in there...
找出一双可以适合你的脚的鞋子
...and pick out any shoes that fit your feet.
我不管它是否搭配 我不管它是否会…
I don't care if they match. I don't care if they make...
让你的脚踝，膝盖，或耳垂 看起来胖胖的，快去吧
...your ankles or your knees or your earlobes look fat. Just do it!
进去房间里，挑出要穿的 然后我们就可以走了
Go in there,pick something out so we can go.
好的 谢谢你
-All right. -Thank you.
我要打给蜜雪儿 确定那是她的声音，抱歉
I've got to call Michelle to see if that was her voice.
没错，那就是她的声音
It was. It was her voice.
莫妮卡，我想你又开始偏执了
Monica,I think you've gone over to the bad place.
（西班牙语）喂？
Hola.
喂…？
Hello? Hello?
好，那是她的声音，对吗？ 绝对是，对啊
-Okay. That was her,right? -Definitely. Yeah.
这样就解决啦
So there you go.
我们的危险解除啦 我要去换衣服了
We're out of the woods. I think I'll get dressed now.
我来接 好
-I'll get it. -Okay.
你好，莫妮卡与瑞秋的家
Hi,Monica and Rachel's.
好，请稍等 请问您是哪位？
Yeah,just a second. Can I ask who's calling?
是蜜雪儿！
It's Michelle!
她一定有来电显示功能 你也该去装一个
She must have that "caller l. D." thing. You should get that.
蜜雪儿？
Michelle?
对，就是我 我不小心拨了你的电话
Yeah,that was me. I dialed your number by mistake.
只要试着…
Just try to be
你真的好贴心
You're so sweet.
是啊，我们是一对很好的情侣
Yeah,we were a great couple.
我知道，我真的很想他
I know,I really miss him.
你也知道的嘛 只不过…
Well,you know how it is. It's just that....
你知道奇怪的是什么？
You know what's weird?
唐老鸭从来不穿裤子
Donald Duck never wore pants.
但是当他洗完澡出来…
But when he gets out of the shower...
他总是在腰间围上一条毛巾
... he always puts a towel around his waist.
我是说，那算什么？
I mean,what is that about?
蜜雪儿，我只是进入答录机 来听我自己的留言
I only beeped in so I could hear my own message.
那样是可以的吧
I mean,that's allowed.
我真的希望你别告诉你爸…
I would really appreciate it if you wouldn't tell your dad about
你说你不高兴是什么意思？ 我们是朋友呢
What do you mean,you don't feel comfortable with this? We're friends!
那个小婊子根本就讨厌我
That bitch always hated me.
我要再打给她
I'm calling her back.
好，好啊 好
-Okay,fine. -Okay.
她房间里有电话吧？ 好，我们来处理吧
-She's got a phone in there,right? -Okay,we're on it.
我知道单子上写 “打领带与否，自行决定”
I know it says "black tie optional"...
但这样会不会太过分了点？
... but this may be pushing it a little.
我不去了
I'm not gonna go.
你不去了？
You're not gonna go?
不，我想更新我的通讯录
No,I think I'm gonna catch up on my correspondence.
你怎么可以不去呢？
How can you not be going?
我就是不去了
I'm not gonna go.
我想这样就表明了 “我不去”的意思
So I think that will accomplish the "not going."
我只是好奇…
You know,just out of curiosity
自从你在我朋友面前 羞辱我，又对我大吼
Ever since I was humiliated and yelled at in front of my friends...
我就没有情绪去参加 什么博物馆的慈善会了
... I'm just,I don't know,not in a very museum benefit-y kind of mood.
好…天啊，很抱歉 我对你大吼大叫，对不起
Right. Well,okay. Okay. God,I'm sorry. I'm sorry I yelled.
没关系 不，可是你在生气
-That's fine. -No,but you're mad.
我没有生气，我只是不去了
I'm not mad. I'm just not going.
是的 好
-Right. -Okay.
你知道我一定要去吧？
You know that I have to go,right?
那这样会不会变成 我在你难过时离你而去？
So is it gonna be,like,I'm abandoning you while you're upset?
不会 不会？
-No. -No?
我对你大吼，你不难过？ 对，还包括你的羞辱
-You're not upset about the yelling. -Right. And the humiliating.
当然，还有羞辱
Well,of course,the humiliating.
那么，我们…
So we...
我们之间没问题？
...we're okay?
我们很好啊 好
-We're good. -Right.
甜心，我爱你 是的，罗斯
-Honey? I love you. -Yes,Ross.
把电话放下！
Get away from that phone!
她已经开始换衣服了
She's just getting dressed now.
我居然因此而兴奋 我是不是有问题？
Is it wrong that I was totally aroused by that?
好啦，兄弟，就是这样啦
Okay,buddy boy,here it is.
你把我衣服藏起来 我就把你所有的衣服穿上
You hide my clothes,I'm wearing everything you own.
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
我把你的内裤藏起来 但这根本不是相反的事
That is so not the opposite of taking somebody's underwear!
你看看我，我是钱德！
Look at me! I'm Chandler.
我还能再多穿一件衣服吗？
Could I be wearing any more clothes?
或许我不该不穿内裤的…
Maybe if I wasn't going commando....
穿这么多真是热死我了
It's hot with all this stuff on.
我最好别再做运动… 像是蹲马步之类的
I better not do any,I don't know,lunges.
够了，别再蹲马步了
Okay,enough. Enough with the lunging.
我快被烦死了 我真的已经受够了
I'm sick of this. I've had it up to here.
你们两个都不准参加晚会！
Neither of you can come to the party!
天啊，真幼稚
Jeez,what a baby!
你干嘛破坏一切 我正要去换衣服了
Way to ruin it. I was just gonna go get dressed.
那个唯一我会在乎 她是否换好衣服的人
The only person I cared about getting dressed...
却是那个不肯去的人
...is the person who's not even gonna go.
瑞秋，我很抱歉，好吗？
Look,Rach,I'm sorry,okay?
我真是个混球 抱歉对你大吼，我希望你能去
Look,I was a jerk,okay? I'm sorry I yelled. I want you there.
我需要你去
I need you there.
要怎样做才能证明 我有多希望你去？
What can I do to show you how much I want you to be there?
你可以把那杯油喝掉
You could drink the fat.
欢迎你进入大人的谈话世界
Welcome to an adult conversation.
不，等一下…
No,no,no. Now wait a minute. Wait a minute.
听起来挺有意思的 什么？
-That actually sounds interesting. -What?
我想你应该把那杯油喝掉
I think you should drink the fat.
好，若这样就能证明 你对我有多重要…
Okay,if that's what it takes to show you how much you mean to me...
以及我多希望你能去 那我就愿意去做
...and how much I want you there,that's what I'll do.
我帮你换一杯 这一杯放好久了
Let me get you another glass. That's been sitting out.
我想这样可以了
I think this will be fine.
好吧，香草奶昔 只不过是香草奶昔…
Okay,vanilla milkshake. Just a vanilla milkshake...
只不过有鸡肉的碎屑浮着
...with chicken bits floating in it.
干杯！
Cheers.
不，不要 好吧，我去就是了…
No,don't! Okay,okay,I'll go. I'll go.
你肯去？
You will?
你真的会那么做，对吧？
You were really gonna do that.
是啊
Well,yeah.
你真的愿意喝下那些油？
You were gonna drink the fat.
我们来看看他还能做什么
Let's see what else he'll do!
不如你现在去换衣服 你把他的内裤还给他
How about you get changed? Give him his underwear.
我来叫计程车 我要大家在两分钟内下楼
I'll get a cab. I want everyone downstairs in two minutes.
莫妮卡！
Monica!
别做了！
Stop it.
别再做了！
Stop it!
罗斯去叫计程车了 那么我们…
Ross went to get a cab,so we
你在做什么？ 不，莫妮卡！
What are you doing? No,Monica,no!
我是理查
Hi,this is Richard.
你有三个新讯息
You have three new messages.
再也没有了
Not anymore.
讯息已删除
Message erased.
请在哔声后留言
To record your message,begin speaking at the tone.
你好，理查，我是莫妮卡
Hi,Richard. It's Monica.
我今晚做了一件很疯狂的事
Listen,I did something kind of crazy tonight.
或许是我经期的原因 我也不晓得
Maybe I'm getting my period or something. I don't know.
反正我进入你的答录机 然后听到一个留言…
Anyway,I beeped into your machine and I heard this message...
快把我搞疯了
...that freaked me out...
其他的蜜雪儿会告诉你
...and Michelle will tell you the rest.
我很抱歉 我希望你忘了这整件事
I'm sorry,okay? And I hope that we can just forget the whole thing.
你的主人留言已经更改
Your outgoing message has now been changed.
主人留言？
Outgoing?
他刚刚是说主人留言？
Did that say outgoing?
不是主人留言！
Not outgoing!
你好，理查，我是莫妮卡
Hi,Richard,it's Monica.
我今晚做了一件疯狂的事
Listen,I did something kind of crazy tonight.
或许是我的经期的原因 我也不晓得
Maybe I'm getting my period or something. I don't know.
你是怎么做的？ 我不知道！
-How did you do that? -I don't know!
再见
Goodbye.
好，我叫到两辆计程车 但还没人坐进去，快！
Okay,I've got two cabs and no people! Go,go,go!
或许我们可以叫电话公司改掉那个留言？
Maybe we can call the phone company to change the message?
或者他们可以把他的电话号码改掉
They could change his number.
我想经过这件事 他会自己改的
I think after this,he'll be doing that himself.
瑞秋！
Rachel!
你…你看起来…
You.... You look....
而我还剩下五秒钟
And I still have about five seconds to spare.
这样大概花掉七秒钟
That was about 7 seconds.
所以我们迟了一点
So we're a little late.
走吧
Come on.
对了…
Oh,and by the way....
什么事？
What?
我里面也没穿…
I'm going commando too.
所以我说：你是谁？麦格农私家侦探吗？
So l said, “Who are you Cro-Magnum P.l.?”
盖勒博士？
Dr. Geller?
我是伦敦研究院的雪曼惠菲 很荣幸见到你
-Sherman Whitfield,London lnstitute. -What a pleasure.
你的前白垩纪化石报告 写得真不错
I was quite impressed with your paper on pre-Cretaceous fossils.
是的，你再次验证了 我以前写的东西
Yes. It confirmed everything I'd written.
对不起
Excuse me.
你好
Hi.
什么事？
Yes?
你好像坐在我的位子上
You're kind of sitting in my seat.
你说你的位子 是什么意思？
What do you mean,your seat?
我是说，我本来坐在这儿 但是你起来了
-I mean,I was sitting there. -But you got up.
可是我没有离开这个房间
But I never left the room.
但是你离开椅子了
But you left the chair area.
好吧，就这样 把你的内裤给我
All right,that's it. Give me your underwear.